I believe one of the greatest impairments to creating real mobilization and cohesive
movements is what I call the nuance of convenience.
And what this is, is the concept of creating nuances that are convenient to an individual's
situation, preference, et cetera, even though it is harmful to the collective.
So this is a result, of course, of this main character energy that we have here in this
colonizer imperial framework, right?
This idea that, well, but if it's good for me, then it's good for the gander when that
simply is not true all the time.
Now, sometimes if it's good for you, it doesn't even affect the gander.
So it's like whatever, but sometimes it does.
And oftentimes we are excluding the greater way that something is affecting people because
it works for us.
And a fabulous example of this is Hannah Bespinder.
I think that's her last name.
She's the young lady who won the Emmy.
And in her Emmy speech, you know, she said F ice, go birds, free Palestine, right?
She's Jewish.
And she talks very earnestly about that.
She is a big supporter of Palestine and the Palestinian people.
And this is very much a part of her Jewish faith.
But she has a Zionist stylist.
That is a nuance of convenience.
There's a nuance that she has created that is convenient for her and that allows her to
ignore this glaring contradiction to her value system.
Individuals who say, eat the rich and there shouldn't be billionaires except for Jay-Z
and Beyonce or except for Taylor Swift.
Nuance of convenience.
Because you're like, but I like their music.
These nuances of convenience also let people off the hook who in their access in their platforms,
et cetera, could be really useful in moving needles forward for change for the greater
good for the collective.
But because they are not challenged to do so, because they get to exist in this protective
bubble of nuance, they're doing them.
And so there's no bottom line.
It's got dashes.
And then dashes is what people keep falling through.
And if we don't got a bottom line, then maybe we can't hold a line.
You feel me?